The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Why do you look different from before ?
Ma Liang was a possessed body.
Of course, I look different.
What you see in front of you
is my real appearance.
Senior,
you said you wanted a pill to breakthrough ?
Yes.
I have a special cultivation method.
I have to rely on this body to breakthrough.
Although you will need many pills to reach Core Formation,
I can make them.
But reaching Nascent Soul
requires much more spiritual energy...
If you take so many pills within such a short time,
Senior will poison himself !
Don't worry,
I use an ancient technique
that allows me to take as many pills as needed.
Then I'll help you breakthrough to Core Formation first.
These pills should be enough.
Here are items I gathered over the years.
See if you can find something valuable here.
Senior,
where did you get this thing ?
This ?
Is it a treasure ?
If we can open this furnace
you will be able to breakthrough.
Really ?
This talisman is called a pill seal.
It feeds a pill with spiritual energy.
According to the records,
it was used on at least grade 6 pills.
Grade 6 ?
No matter what the effect of this pill is,
it will have enough energy to form a Nascent Soul.
But...
the method to open a pill seal has been lost to time.
If we open it forcefully,
the quality of the pill will drop.
It may even
turn the pill to ashes.
This jade belonged to the person who owned it.
See if you can find a way to break the seal.
In this jade,
there are just pill recipes.
There isn't such a method...
It's fine.
Senior, focus on reaching Core Formation.
As for opening the pill seal,
leave it to Wan'er.
Senior,
this is a grade 2 Yellow Spring Pill,
it will expand your meridians
so you should take it first.
But it's very toxic
so you have to be careful.
This is a Three Purification Pill,
it will cleanse your meridians, easing the flow of spiritual energy.
This is a Mystic Ice Pill,
it will help you with your cold-type cultivation.
This is the Thousand Chances Pill,
it can absorb the essence of the world.
The Barrier Breaking Pill
will dissipate the barriers
formed in your body by pills.
This is the Primordial Unity Pill,
it's a tonic.
How can you swallow a Primordial Unity Pill like a candy !?
I worked hard to get one when I was alive...
This one is also a treasure !
You're wasting them...
You're just forming your Core,
you should be ashamed !
One more step, I will combine the three Cold Cores.
and reach Core Formation.
A Heaven Separating Pill ?
Senior !
Senior...
This is a Heaven Separating Pill made from Demon Blood Vine.
Its effect isn't... as good.
But !
It seems
the pill seal needs a lot of energy to be opened.
Mystic Wild Grass,
cold type.
It has the effect of absorbing spiritual energy.
This may be it !
I just need a few excipients
and I can try to break open the pill seal.
What have you two found out in the month of spying on her ?
Elder Li's research was all over the place.
From pill recipes to meditation effects.
According to our observations,
there wasn't anything that stood out.
Did she record anything ?
Yes,
but it's equally as random.
It's as if she didn't have a goal.
Young Master,
as a top 3 alchemist of the Cloud Sky Sect,
Elder Li is very clever and cautious.
She hid her search among other things.
If that's the truth,
then she has succeeded.
Incompetent fools !
What's the point of being angry at them ?
Look at you,
you don't look like an elder.
I'm sorry, we're leaving.
Father,
your son almost died !
That ghost
appeared in front of me !
If I didn't have that spirit bell,
I'd be no more than a piece of flesh !
In the past few days,
only that bitch's friend entered the Cloud Sky Sect.
It must have something to do with her.
I want them dead !
Don't worry,
if that coward kid dares to show up again,
I will definitely make him pay for it.
You just need to prepare for the wedding.
I don't have enough spiritual energy.
I have to go back to the Library
to find a way to increase it.
Get out.
Don't bother my cultivation.
We are about to get married.
Why are you so cold ?
I forgot to ask you earlier.
What's your relationship
with that man ?
Does this also need to be reported to Elder Sun ?
Wan'er,
the sect made a lot of preparations.
Look,
they sent a gift in advance.
Do you like it ?
You can think that I don't care
but you are very important to me.
I won't let you run away.
This marriage
will go through
even if you don't want to.
The Sect Leader has ordered that
Elder Li cannot leave the Southern Courtyard.
She will prepare
for the Dual Cultivation ceremony.
Without a direct order from the Cloud Sky Sect,
she cannot leave.
Understood !
Wang Lin's avatar
Early stage Core Formation
Oh my god.
In just a month,
Master already reached Core Formation !
Disc...iple...
You...
really reached Core Formation ?
As expected
of Teacher's old friend.
Should I... call you Uncle ?
You kindly taught me alchemy.
You don't have to be so polite.
Is something going on with Wan'er ?
Teacher was grounded by Sun Zhenwei.
She cannot leave
the Southern Courtyard.
I'm afraid this will go on
until the ceremony is over.
She asked me to give you this jade.
Senior,
Wan'er's is fine.
Don't worry.
The pill seal needs a lot of spiritual energy
to be opened safely.
Wan'er is trapped in the Southern Courtyard,
unable to find the required herbs.
Now,
I can only think of only one way.
There is a talisman at the top floor of the Library.
If you can get it,
we will borrow the power
of the Heaven Stealing Furnace
to open the pill seal.
The top floor of the Library is very strange.
I heard that when it was being built,
the sect spent a lot of money
to hire a cultivator from a rank 4 country.
He came to polish the white jade pillars.
It was only completed a few months ago.
Moreover,
a Nascent Soul Elder guards it nonstop.
If you want to take that talisman,
it won't be easy.
This jade pillar
has defensive restrictions on it.
Lu Fei
Outer Cloud Sky Sect Elder
Early stage Nascent Soul
You dare enter the Library of the Cloud Sky Sect ?
You deserve to be executed.
Even with restrictions, there is still a guard.
This means that
the restriction only snares
while the cultivator attacks.
I can't beat a Nascent Soul myself.
But with these restrictions in my hands
an Early stage Nascent Soul
cannot defeat me either.
How can he control the restrictions !?
This guy must be caught !
You overestimate yourself !
No matter how powerful you are,
you're still just a Core Formation brat.
What kind of spell is this ?
You brat !
Just you wait !
With my Core Formation cultivation
I can only bind him.
When I use the flag at Nascent Soul
I wonder how strong it will be.
Did you hear ?
That thief
not only stole a talisman
but then he completely vanished.
The Nascent Soul Elders are worried.
Everyone in the sect is being interrogated.
The Nascent Soul Elders
investigated using their Divine Sense.
Master is only at Core Formation
but his Divine Sense is stronger than theirs.
Even after probing him
they couldn't find anything.
3 days later
Ouyang Zi
Master Alchemist of the Cloud Sky Sect
Early stage Nascent Soul
The hour of Yin has come.
Everyone,
open the furnace.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.